This is What We Think of Human Beings.
ReGOREgitated Sacrifice is a horror film directed by Lucifer Valentine.
Guided by identical twin demon spirits, The Black Angels of Hell, we see the diabolical depiction of the alternate-parallel dimension of the simultaneous suicide deaths of Kurt Cobain
and bulimic porn star Angela Aberdeen, as seen through the mental activity of Angela's journey toward brain death as a result of her self-inflicted death by drowning.
Angela Aberdeen, played by Ameara Lavey.
Black Angel of Hell, played by Jen Soska.
Black Angel of Hell, played by Sylvia Soska.
Stepdaughter / Teen Porn Star, played by Isabelle Styles.
Miss Lake Washington, played by Amy Lee.
Stepmother, played by Honey.
The Vomit Gore Trilogy is a feature film trilogy of Canadian surrealist extreme horror films written and directed by Shawn
Fedorchuk (as Lucifer Valentine) with the first two instalments produced by Randy Price (as No One Body).
Fedorchuk coined "vomit gore" as a new subgenre to describe the trilogy, which follows a nonlinear narrative
that centers around teenage runaway Angela Aberdeen, a stripper who suffers from bulimia.
The trilogy focuses primarily on situations involving vomiting,
cannibalism, graphic sexual violence, gore, torture, and murder.
All three of the films received limited theatrical releases, and
were released on DVD by distributor Unearthed Films.
The trilogy was mostly panned by critics, who criticized its
obscenity and depictions of violence against women.
The tone is dark.